

PROFILE

I am a student of Computer Science and Engineering at Vellore Institute of Technology, Vellore.

I love to play around with new embedded technology and portable devices running Android. Worked on many Android devices in the past, including devices running MediaTek and Qualcomm chipsets. I have also played around with different operating systems for ARM chipsets like Ubuntu Touch.

I also happen to be the Founder and Director of a simple, secure and stable AOSP-derived aftermarket operating system, the Styx Project.

CONTACT

PHONE: +91 944 91 16454

WEBSITE: https://malvi.ml

EMAIL: malvigagan@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Reading books Music Android development

GAGAN MALVI

Student

EDUCATION

Kendriya Vidyalaya, NAL

2008 - 2018

Scored 91% in CBSE board examinations

Sri Chaitanya Techno School, Krishnarajapuram

2018 - 2020

Scored 90% in CBSE board examinations

Vellore Institute of Technology, Vellore

2020 - 2024

WORK EXPERIENCE

Paranoid Android, Device Engineer

2020 - Present

Device engineer for the Redmi 9 Power and Redmi Note 4X

Styx Project, Founder and Director

2020 - Present

AOSP-derived aftermarket firmware supporting 25+ devices

Teracube, OSS Developer

2020 - Present

Leading aftermarket development efforts for Teracube devices.

ACM-VIT, Core Committee Member

2021 - Present

App developer team member

VIT Linux Users Group, Core Committee Member

2021 - Present

Lead developer of Arcadia Linux

SKILLS

- C, C++
- Android AOSP and BSP development for MediaTek and Qualcomm chipsets
- Kernel development